Come on, hurry up.
（ニャムサス）ほら　さっさと　おし
呪いで猫に　なりたかないだろ？
You don't want to turn into a cat, do you?
Shut up!
（潤平）うるせえ　わかってるよ
（キャバ猫）頼むぜ→
I know that already!
I'm countin' on ya.
It's my mistress' super favorite.
ウチのご主人の超オキニでさ～
（タマ）骨は拾って
さしあげやすよ　ダンナ
We'll take care of your bones, Master.
Don't be so pessimistic!
縁起でもねえこと言うな
（加奈子）はあ～　何か
いいバイト　ねえかなあ
Are there any good jobs around?
コスメ代も　バカになんねえし
I need money for cosmetics.
ヨッシャー　取ったど～
うん？
Yeah! I got it!
何やってんだ　アイツ？
What the hell's he doing?
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari da
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai
might prove to be a big opportunity.
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo muite miyou
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyan darou
It's really a cat's power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 02!
That guy... A servant?
何で俺が　こんな目に…
Why do I have to suffer?
（タマ）そうそう　まだ１つ
お伝えしてなかったことが…
Oh yeah, there's one more thing we haven't told you.
あッ？
（ニャムサス）呪いのことは→
Don't tell anyone about the curse,
決して　他の人間に話さず→
and don't let anyone notice it.
悟られないよ～に　するんだよ
I'd never talk about this crappy curse.
誰が話すか　…ンなクソ呪い
If anyone does find out,
（タマ）もしも　バレちまったら
その人間に　災いが降りかかる上に
呪いの進行も増すそうですぜ
they'll be cursed too, and your curse will deepen more quickly.
早く言えよ！
You should've said that sooner!
I almost told your owner about it!
危うく　お前のご主人に
相談するとこだったぞ
ニャ～　あの人は　いっぺん
痛い目に　あった方がいいんでさあ
Actually, he needs to get hurt once.
《（鼻歌）》
《（住職）う～ん　これでよし》
All set.
《同伴　ヨロシクでーす》
Here I come, my Japanese girl companions.
《日本の嬢の皆さ～ん》
Well, basically, you've got to deal with this problem yourself.
まッ　自分のケツは
自分で　ふけってことさ→
せいぜい　頑張りな
Just give it your best.
〈まッ　バレなきゃ　いいだけの話〉
I just need to keep it to myself.
（鈴）何か最近
潤平兄ちゃん　変じゃない？
Hasn't Junpei been acting weird recently?
（母）さあ　年頃なんだろ
Dunno. I guess he's at that age.
Hey, your Culture Festival is this week, right?
ねえ　確か　今週って
文化祭だったよね→
Can I come see it?
見に行っても　いい？
Yeah, whatever.
うん　好きにすれば
好きにすればとな！
"Whatever..."
潤平兄ちゃんのクラスって
何　やるの？
What's your class planning to do?
う…　まあ　その　何だ
Well... uh...
《（晴彦）ご主人様に　忠実》
We're always obedient to our masters!
We're clean and elegant!
《そして　清楚で可憐》
And on top of that, we're cute too: maids!
《なおかつ　その容姿もカワイイ
メイドさん！》
メイド　イン　萌え
Maids are so moe.
Whatever.
あっそ
テンション低くね？　潤平キュンキュ～ン
You've gotta be more excited, dear Junpei-kun!
そんな設定で
水野が　ご奉仕してくれるんだよ
Mizuno will be wearing that costume as she serves you!
Service!
ご奉仕！？
Yes, Master.
《（楓）ご主人様　ご主人様》
Master, you have food stuck on your cheek.
《ご主人様　お口に食べこぼしが
ついておられますよ》
≪（加奈子）お～い　高坂～
Hey, Kousaka...
《ハサミ　貸して～》
Let me borrow your scissors.
ギャーーーッ
いきなり　出てくんな
Don't pop up so suddenly, Yamanba monster!
The Yamanba is a spirit from Japanese folklore, usually portrayed as an old hag.
妖怪　山姥
いやッ　住吉　加奈子！
I mean, Sumiyoshi Kanako!
Kana-chan, have you got any scissors?
カナちゃ～ん　ハサミ借りられた？
〈水野！？〉
Mizuno!
Sorry. Give me another minute.
ああ　悪い　ちょっと待って
Here you go.
どうぞ
あ　ありがとう？
Th-Thank you.
Koubaka, you piece of shit!
高バカ　テメエ！
ああッ　誰が　「高バカ」だ
俺の名字は　「高坂」だっつーの
You callin' me KouBAKA?!
My name is KouSAKA!
いい加減にしろよ　テメエ
Stop giving me crap, damn it!
Same to you!
そりゃ　こっちのセリフだ
山姥じゃねえ　マンバだ　マンバ！
It's not Yamanba!
It's Manba!
Manba is a fashion style involving the use of very dark makeup.
Shut up!
うるせーッ
妖怪は　長屋か横町に帰れ！
Go back to your own world, monster!
（晃太）また　始まったな
There they go again.
I'll bet my yakisoba bread that Kanako wins.
（男子Ａ）「今日も　加奈子が勝つ」に
やきそばパン
I'll bet 50 yen on Kousaka.
（Ｂ）大穴　高坂に５０円
安～い
You're so cheap.
Please get back to work!
（委員長）皆さん　作業してください
賭け事は　禁止
And no betting!
They're such good friends.
やあ～　ホントに仲いいよね～
幼なじみで　クラスが一緒って
いいなあ
I'm envious that both of them have a childhood friend in class.
What?
（栄子・ヒナ子）どこが！？
そんな態度　とっていいのか？
You sure you wanna act like that?
コイツ　小３の運動会のとき…
When he was in third grade...
でもって　小４で…
Then in fourth grade...
You dirty piece of crap, Sumiyoshi!
汚ねえぞ　住吉！
Sir!
ダンナ～
うん？　どうした？
What is it?
ドラーッ…
フニャッ…
Why?!
ハッ！？　いけね
ちょっと取ってくるわ
Crap, I'll go get that.
何？
Huh?
…たく　もう　男子は
Typical boys.
Are you okay, Kanako?
加奈子　大丈夫？
おッ　おう…
Y-Yeah.
お前ら　何で　ここに
Why are you here?
What else?
（タマ）決まってまさあ　出番ですぜ
You've got a job.
（ニャムサス）あれが　今回の依頼猫だよ
The requesting cat is over there.
ああ？
（くまねこ）ども
Hello.
Don't tell me you...
まさか　お前…
Didn't you know?
（ニャムサス）知らなかったのかい？
この子　ここに住んでんのさ
She lives here.
They're even at school.
〈学校にまで…〉
So much for my modest sanctuary!
〈俺の
ささやかな安らぎプレイスが〉
But there's a reason why I'll be moving out soon.
（くまねこ）とはいえ　このたび
訳あって　ここを離れることに…
A teacher found out about her.
（タマ）センセに
見つかっちまったんでさあ
So, I want to express my appreciation to the kind girl who fed me every day.
で　毎日　欠かさず
ご飯をくれた　優しいお嬢さんに
お礼を伝えたいんです
「本当に　ありがとう
大好きです」　と
"Thank you very much! I really love you!"
俺が　そんな羞恥プレー　できっか
コノヤローッ
Me?
Don't make me do something so embarrassing!
どんな女の子なんですかねえ
What's that girl like?
（くまねこ）そうですねえ
優しくて　いい匂いがして→
Well...
She's really kind,
smells good,
そうそう
ちょうどアナタと同じくらいです
and oh yeah, she's just about the same age as you.
Same age?
俺と？　同学年ってことか
So, in the same grade.
A girl of the same age, plus a cat,
divided by the diligence of the care,
multiplied by a good, kind smell, equals...
Mature glasses
girl type
But thank you.
《伝言　ありがとうございます》
I like gentle people like you.
《そんな優しいアナタが好き》
Pure class
rep type
Will you fill the gap in my heart left by that kitty?
《あの子を失った心の穴》
《アナタが埋めてくれますか？》
そんな　急に言われましても
Oh, but that's so sudden...
（ニャムサス）
気持ち悪い子だねえ→
Weirdo.
You have to finish by tomorrow.
タイムリミットは　明日まで
すぐに　何とかしな
Get to work right now.
Y-Yeah.
Hold on a sec!
おい　待て
俺には俺の生活が　あんだよ！
I have my own life too!
Master, someone will hear you if you talk so loud.
（タマ）ダンナ　あんまり大声出すと
誰かに　聞こえますぜ
I can't work for you all the friggin' time!
年がら年中　お前らに
つきあってられっかっつーの
（ニャムサス）な～
わかってるよ
I know!
（くまねこ）うな～
そんだけで　わかるか
I need more info.
≪（タマ）ニャ～
これだから　猫は…
This is why I hate cats.
（くまねこ）ニャ～　ニャ～
ああ？　何だよ
What is it?
住吉ッ！
Sumiyoshi?!
Hey, there's a familiar face.
（ニャムサス）おや　見覚えのある顔だね
Onee-chan.
おねえちゃん
よお～　くまねこ
Hey, Kumaneko.
It's YOU?!
…て　お前かーーッ！
What!
ンだよ　アタシが
猫かわいがってちゃ　悪いのかよ
You got a problem with me being kind to a cat?
I do!
悪いよ　俺の妄想…
青春を返せ　バッキャロー！
Give back my fantasies— my good luck, damn it!
（加奈子）何だと！？
（ニャムサス）コラッ　依頼は　どうした？→
What?!
Hey, what about her request?
オトコなら　早く言っちまいな
Be a man and say it right now.
Please tell her.
言ってください
ここで言えば　楽になりやすぜ
You'll feel good if you tell her now.
R-Right, I should just go ahead and tell her.
〈そうか　ここはもう
勢いで言っちまった方が…〉
Thank you so very much!
《本当に　ありがとう
大好きです！》
I love you!
by Panda
《超キモい》
Gross.
Hell no!
…て　言えるかーい！
Wait a sec.
〈待てよ　これって　ヤバくね？〉
Isn't this bad?
Wait, stay calm.
〈いや　落ち着け〉
I didn't tell her about the curse.
〈呪いの話は　してねえし
大したことは…〉
What's important is...
〈でも　どう見ても　今の俺って
猫と会話してた変人！？〉
I must've looked like a weirdo who was talking to cats.
〈誰かに　言いふらされる前に
軽く流せば…〉
If I laugh it off before she starts spreading the word...
なあ　住吉…
Hey, Sumiyoshi...
いいネタ　発見
What a scoop.
I can't laugh it off!
〈流せねえ～
絶対　言われる～ッ〉
She's gonna blab!
ニャ～ン
ああ　お前…
Hey, you're...
（加奈子）なあ　高坂→
Hey Kousaka, you'll do whatever I ask, won't you?
お前　アタシの言うこと
何でも聞くよな？
はあ？
今　ちょうど欲しかったんだよね
I was just looking for...
a servant.
下僕が
Dad, do you think I can fulfill this request safely?
〈父さん
僕　今回の依頼〉
〈無事に　果たせるでしょうか…〉
住吉　加奈子
猫　好き
Sumiyoshi Kanako.
I love... cats.
What the hell are you looking at?
どこ見てんのよ　始まるわよ
It's about to begin.
Let's see, the next delivery is...
（千鶴）え～と　次のお届け先は…
The 30th Tokiwa High School Cultural Festival
へえ～　楽しそうだなあ
Hm, that looks like fun.
（校内放送）「本日　１２時より
体育館にて　演劇部による…」
At noon, there will be a presentation
by the drama club in the gymnasium.
Welcome home.
お帰りなさいませ
ただいま
Hello.
Order coming in.
オーダー　ホットティー　２つね
（晃太）うい～
Two hot teas.
K.
Also—
それと…
すいません　失礼しま～す
Hello, excuse me.
Uh...
ああ　えっと…
おおッ　鈴ちゃん　久しぶり
何　飲む　飲む～？
Oh, Suzu-chan, long time no see.
What do you want to drink?
Oh?
あれ　２人だけ？　高坂は？
さあ
Only the two of you here?
Where's Kousaka?
Dunno.
住吉に拉致されて以来　見てないよ
I haven't seen him since Sumiyoshi snatched him.
A curse on...
う～ら～め～し～
Man, that's super scary!
おーッ　超怖～
キャーッ！
アハハッ　ここは
お化けが絶叫する屋敷かよ
In this haunted house, it's the ghosts that scream?
アハハハッ　マジ　ウケる～
That rocks!
Why do I have to suffer like this?
何で　俺が
こんな目に…
〈晴彦のバカによると…〉
According to that nitwit Haruhiko...
《幼なじみは　よいフラグです→》
Childhood friends are a promising flag.
In elementary school, they're just very good friends.
《小学校　とにかく仲よし→》
They may show an "I'll be your bride" flag too.
《「将来は
お嫁さんになる」　フラグも→》
In junior high, they're temporarily separated into different classes.
《中学生　しばしの別れ
クラス分けイベント発生→》
However!
《が　高校で再会　そして伝説へ→》
They meet again in high school, and the legend continues.
We'll meet under the tree!
《樹のもとへ！》
That's what he says, but...
〈らしいが…〉
Nope.
〈ないわ～〉
Only if she were Mizuno...
〈水野だったらなあ〉
おッ
今度は　あっち行ってみようぜ
Hey, let's check out what's happening over there.
おわッ
Oh, Kana-chan.
あッ　カナちゃん
Hey, Kaede.
おおッ　楓
…と　高坂くん？
And Kousaka-kun?
水野！　これは…
Mizuno! This is...
You heading to the classroom now?
楓達　そろそろ？
Yeah.
うん　教室
And we were just talking about inviting you too.
今ちょうど　「カナちゃんも一緒に」
って話してたんだけど…
Would you come with us when you're free?
いつでも　かまわないから
後で　一緒してね
〈気を使われた？〉
She's being considerate to Kanako.
Thanks.
おう　悪いな
コイツ　今日が初陣なんよ
This is his first day as my servant.
アタシの下僕になって
〈（栄子・ヒナ子）下僕？〉
Her servant...
So I'll come over after I'm through with him.
つーわけで　た～っぷり
コキ使ってから　そっち行くわ
うん　待ってるね～
Okay. We'll be expecting you.
Later.
またな～
高坂く～ん　ファイトだよ
Kousaka-kun, fight-o!
〈みッ　水野ーーーッ！〉
Mizuno!
やあ～　ホントいいよねえ
I envy them.
幼なじみで　しかも　あんなに…
Childhood friends, and very close ones at that.
いや　だから…
下僕って…
Um, but...
Her servant...
She made me buy a lot.
だいぶ　買わされたが
今　いくら残ってんだ？
How much do I have left?
Crap!
ゲッ　クッソ～　住吉のヤツ
Damn it!
Sumiyoshi, damn it!
調子に乗りやがって…
You've gone too far!
（ニャムサス）泣きブリッジ中　失礼するよ
Excuse me for intruding into your crying fit.
ニャムサス
ホントに　やる気　あんのかい？
Nyamsus.
Do you have any intention of fulfilling the request?
依頼の締め切りは
今日なんだけどね
It's due today.
I know that!
わあってるよ　でも…
But...
That girl used to come to our home a lot, didn't she?
あの小娘
昔よく　ウチに来てた子だろ？
ちょいと面相は
変わっちまってるけど→
Her appearance has changed a bit, but I could tell right away.
すぐ　わかったよ
覚えてたのか
You remember?
まんざら
知らぬ仲じゃ　あるまいし
You know her, so finish quickly.
サラッと　すませちまいな
Give me a break!
冗談　言うな
ひと事だと思って
That's easy for you to say.
Besides, because she looks like that,
それに　今の住吉
あんな見た目だし
何か　話しづらくなってなあ
it's not easy to talk to her anymore.
うん　こんなモンかあ？
Yup, that should do it.
Now, what should we do next?
さ～て　次は　何すっかなあ
何か　ちょっと
ガキの頃を思い出すぜ
This reminds me of our days as kids.
《潤平》
《う　うん？》
Junpei...
《これ　やるよ》
This is for you.
《うお～　ニャムだあ！》
It's Nyam!
《これ　お前が作ったのか？》
Did you make this?
Yeah. It's for our friendship.
《おう　友情の証しだ》
《大切にしろよ》
Take good care of it.
Yeah!
《おう！　サンキュー》
Thanks!
≪（加奈子）けど　次の日すぐ…
But the very next day...
It's so cute!
《わあ～　カワイイ》
《潤平くん　ありがとう》
Thank you, Junpei-kun.
《高バカ　テメエ！》
Koubaka, you idiot!
《うわ～ッ！》
We stopped talking after that.
≪（加奈子）それから　お互い
口きかなくなって→
In junior high, we waged a cold war.
中ボーの頃は　冷戦状態→
高校じゃ　よりによって
また同じクラスに…
And now in high school, we're in the same class again.
〈まッ　どーせ　アイツは
ろくに覚えてやしねえだろうけど〉
But I'm sure he doesn't remember any of it.
潤平のヤツ…
Does Junpei...
やっぱ　アタシと　いるより→
enjoy Kaede's company more than mine?
楓と一緒の方が　楽しいのかな
What's taking her so long?
〈おっせーな　住吉のヤツ〉
≪（加奈子）おう　待たせたな
あッ
Hey, thanks for waiting.
素人が焼いたモンだけど
けっこう　イケるぜ
This was made by amateurs, but it's pretty good.
お前の金だ　遠慮すんなよ　下僕
I bought it with your money, so don't hold back, servant.
I've been wanting to ask you...
前から　いっぺん
聞きたかったんだが
何で　今どき　マンバ？
Why the manba makeup?
ああッ？　悪いかよ
What's wrong with it?!
好きで　やってんだよ
文句あっか？
I just like it!
Got a problem with that?!
いや…
No.
It makes me feel stronger.
何か　強くなった気　すんだよ
もう　メソメソ泣きたかねえしな
I don't want to cry like a girl anymore.
やっぱ　覚えてねえか
I guess you don't remember.
Now, I wanna avoid turning into a cat,
〈さて　猫には　なりたかねえし〉
〈どうやって
依頼を果たしたもんか…〉
so how do I fulfill the request?
Do you hate being with me that much?
そんなに　アタシと一緒に
いたくねえのかよ
Watching your face just pisses me off!
お前の顔　見てっと
ホント　イラッとくるわ～
Why did we have to be in the same high school?
何で　ンな高校
入っちまったんだろう
Why are you mumbling and then getting pissed?!
何　ブツクサ言って
勝手に　キレてんだあ？
Besides, you started the fight when we were kids!
ガキの頃
ケンカ　ふっかけてきたのは
オメエじゃねえか！　一体…
Do you—
Man, you only remember that stuff.
変なことばっか覚えてるくせに
お　お　おい…
H-H-Hey...
お前は　忘れてんのに
アタシばっか　覚えてて
You've forgotten, but I remember...
Making me feel like an idiot!
バカみてえじゃねえか！
えーッ　泣いてる～！？
What, crying?
もういい　帰る
Forget it.
I'm leaving.
Wait!
ちょッ　待てって
離せ！
Let me go!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?!
すいませーん　大丈夫ですか？
〈ああ…　ツイてねえ〉
So unlucky.
Kousaka!
高坂ーーーッ！
W-Wait! I didn't do any—
まッ　待って
俺は　何も
テメエ！
うわーーッ
Wait!
ゴラーーーッ→
Wait, damn it!
待て　ゴラーーッ！
I'm cursed enough already!
呪いなら　間に合ってまーす！
あれ？　今の…
Hm? Weren't they...
ああ～　気持ち悪ッ
Man, I feel sick.
Don't make a couch potato run except in P.E. class.
帰宅部を　体育以外で
ダッシュさせんなっつーの
テメエが逃げるから
But you're the one who ran away.
It's not summer, so I'm not using waterproof makeup.
夏じゃねえし
ウオータープルーフ　使ってねえのに
It all washed off.
化粧　全部　落ちたべ～
マジ最悪
This sucks.
Kousaka!
高坂ーッ！
それで　ふけ～ッ
Dry yourself with this!
It's better than nothing.
ないよか　マシだろ
Right. Sumiyoshi is a girl after all.
〈そっか
住吉も　一応　女だったな〉
〈昔っから
男みたいなヤツだったけど〉
She was always a tomboy.
I guess she can be cute sometimes.
〈まあ
ちったあ　カワイイとこも…〉
〈そっか　アイツ　もしかして…〉
Oh right, maybe she's...
なあ　住吉
さっきの話だけど
Hey, Sumiyoshi,
about what you were saying earlier..
ああッ　スッピンなんだよ
I don't have any makeup on now!
急に　こっち見んな　バカッ
Don't look at me, idiot!
Hey now...
あのなあ…
ああ　いた　いた
There you are.
２人とも　足　速いねえ
ビックリしたよ～
You both run really fast.
That surprised me.
Thank you very much!
〈ありがとうございま～す〉
Thump
Kaede! I can't serve my shift like this!
楓～　こんなんじゃ
当番　できねえよ　どうしよう
What should I do?
Oh my.
あらら…　とりあえず
風邪ひいちゃうと　いけないから
You might catch a cold, so let's go to the locker room and change.
更衣室　行って
着替えよう　ねッ
Okay?
Yeah.
Kousaka-kun, I'm going to borrow Kana-chan for a bit.
高坂くん
ちょっと　カナちゃん　借りてくね
えッ！？　ええ　ご自由に…
Yeah, be my guest.
〈水野…　やっぱり勘違いしてる〉
Mizuno's really mistaken about us.
高坂　クビ！
Kousaka, you're fired!
代わりに　私
手伝っといたからね～
I helped out in your place.
すみませんでした
I'm sorry.
何だ？
What?
I shouldn't!
やっぱ　恥ずいって
大丈夫　大丈夫　ほら
Don't worry. Don't worry!
See?
おおッ　ポイント高～ッ
わあッ
She's a beauty!
けど　あんな女子
ウチのクラスに　いたっけ？
But do we have a girl like that in our class?
Could it be...
まさか…
薄化粧だと　逆に恥ずかしいんだよ
Light makeup is even more embarrassing.
Geez.
も～う　モトがいいんだから
もったいないよ　カナちゃん
You have good face, so don't let it go to waste, Kana-chan.
カナ…
ちゃん？
Kana...
...chan?
（一同）住吉ッ！？
Sumiyoshi?!
ンだよッ　見んじゃねえ　ほらッ！
What?!
Stop staring!
〈女って　怖いと思いました〉
I've realized how scary women are.
Hey, Kumaneko!
≪（加奈子）お～い　くまねこ～→
Time for food!
エサだぞ～　お～い
Hey!
Kuma!
くま～
おっかしいなあ
Strange...
いつもなら　すぐ来んのに
She usually comes out right away.
高坂？
あ…　あの猫なら
Kousaka?
I-If you're looking for that cat,
I think she moved somewhere else.
他んトコに　移ったみたいだぜ
S-So, uh, thank you for all the...
そッ　そんで…　いッ　今まで
ありが…
アナタが　だ・い・好き…
And I love...
そっか
アイツ　いなくなっちゃったのか
I see. So she moved away.
まあ　もともと野良だったしな
She was a stray cat anyway.
H-Hey.
あッ　あのなあ
うん？
あの猫　その…
That cat... um...
世話してくれた　お前に
すげえ感謝してんだろうし
I think she really appreciated all the care you gave her,
幸せだったと思う
and I think she was happy.
いきなり　何　言ってんの？
What's all this?
〈言うと思った〉
I knew she'd say that.
猫ってさ
３日で　恩　忘れるっていうじゃん
You know that cats forget favors in three days.
くまねこも　誰かさんみたく
I'm sure Kumaneko will forget about me quickly, just like a certain someone.
すぐ　アタシのこと
忘れちゃうんだろうな
あッ　あの人形！
A-A-About that doll...
ただ　見せてただけで
あげてねえからな
I was only showing it. I didn't give it away.
ウチに　まだ　あるし
It's still at home.
俺みてえに
忘れることも　あるだろうけど
That cat might forget stuff like I do,
あの猫だって
世話になった人間のことは
but I think she'll remember someone who took care of her for so long.
ずっと覚えてると思うぞ
お前　さっきから　変じゃね？
You're acting weird.
お…　俺は
猫の気持ちが　わかるの！
I-I can tell how cats feel!
マジで言ってんの？
You serious about that?
…おう
Yeah.
そっか
I see.
バッカじゃねえの
That's so dumb.
まッ　慰めには　なったよ
じゃあな　潤平
But you've cheered me up.
Later, Junpei.
お…　おう
Y-Yeah.
これで　いいか？
You satisfied with that?
（くまねこ）ニャ～ン
元気でな
Take care.
Wait just a minute!
…て　おいッ　何で　俺んちに？
Why is she at my home?!
（ニャムサス）
いい物件が　見つかるまでだとさ
It's only until she finds a good place to live.
それより　アンタ
これから　どうするよ？
Anyway, what are you going to do now?
ああ？　どうするって？
What do you mean?
もちろん
１日も早く解くぜ　呪いを！
I'll lift the curse as fast as I can, of course!
（ニャムサス）そうじゃなくてさ…
I know, but that's not what I meant.
U-Um, Mizuno,
あ　あの…　水野
昨日のことだけど…
うん？
about yesterday...
≪（加奈子）よッ
おっはよ～　お前ら～
Hey, morning, guys.
わあ～　カナちゃん
やっぱ　そっちの方が　いいよ
Kana-chan! You look better this way!
何で？
別に
But why?
No reason.
まあ
メーク代も　バカになんねえしな
The cosmetics were pretty expensive.
昨日　遊んじまった分
今日は　働くぜ
Because I goofed off, I'll work hard today!
うん！
ホントかよ
Yeah!
You sure?
テンメー　このッ
Why you!
何か文句　あんのかよッ
痛てて…
You got a problem?!
It's spring.
春ですなあ
秋だよ　晴彦
It's fall now, Haruhiko.
フラグ　立ちましたなあ
はッ？
The flag is up.
Huh?
そこ　人間的に押しちゃダメ
痛たッ
As a person, you shouldn't try so hard!
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru honokana sugata
I see your silhouette chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow.
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
strawberry tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma!
Today's Mew view
The second half sucked!
お…　俺は
猫の気持ちが　わかるの！
I-I can tell how cats feel!
マジで言ってんの？
おう
You serious about that?
Yeah.
That's so dumb.
I'll go tell everyone!
Damn...
Damn cats!
Mew view
Brr, brr!
Girls are really super realists.
By the way, female cats mature fully in about a year.
Now, the next Nyan Koi...
I'm Mochizuki Chizuru.
I'm a college student working as a delivery girl in this area.
バッカじゃねえの
おお～
A delivery girl with no sense of direction?!
みんなに　言おーっと
You're a high school student, right, Junpei-kun?
ヒザから…　バカヤローッ！
Y-Yes!
Are you old enough to be interested in a woman's body?
ゾゾーッ　女の子って
ホント　超リアリスト
Sexual harassment?!
ちなみに　猫のメスは
約１年ぐらいで　大人になるよ
Next Nyan Koi, the 3rd nyan-ko, "Your Name Is!"
You're blushing! So cute!
It's good to be young!
S-Strange person.